But wait, there's more. There's one more
thing. I just had a 15minute
conversation, I kid you not, with
codeex. We talked about the best place
to deploy this on the internet and we
agreed that using fly.io, the company
behind sprites.dev would be a great
choice for deploying a container asis.
It wrote a script for me. We ran the
script. We've deployed. And you're
looking here, if you just look at the
URL up there, you are looking at
finally-ed.fly.dev.
This is deployed live on the internet.
The AI chat works. The uh the portfolio
is there. The market data is live. We
set up the environment variables
correctly. Everything is running. This
is now deployed. And deployment took all
of 15 minutes. And you should do it too.
So here finally, I leave you. I leave
you finally with the project finally
deployed on the internet with live
market data and a nice light look to
boot. And so take a last look at the
different orchestrators that we've used.
I would say that my favorite experience
is with Claude agent teams and the
winner of the prize in this case was
probably Codeex. It did a fine job
there. And of course, I used it through
sprite dev, which is such a powerful way
to use these these uh agents because you
can use a coding agent in YOLO mode and
feel completely secure, which is great.
So, uh the big challenge for you now is
to take the repo as it stands and give
one of these things a try. If you're
using a free model, maybe you're using
open code with with a a free model or an
open source cheap model, then you will
have you may have a more challenging
experience. Maybe using something as
disciplined as GSD is your way of
getting there. If you are splashing out
and using something like little code,
then you should have an easy old time
with it. But see if you can't challenge
it to do something a bit different.
Maybe you want to add in a kind of the
the users table so different people can
log in as we had it in week two in the
SAS legal platform. Add in that
functionality as well. So take it in
your direction. Remember the amazing
thing about these coding agents is that
it's a choose your own adventure story.
You've got a really robust specification
there in the form of the claude.md. And
now you can build something and take it
somewhere new. Give yourself your own
trader workstation and enjoy it and see
whether you get similar outcomes to me
and whether you find that that Claude or
Codeex or some other model is the winner
and let me know. Share your results
please on on Udemy. Tell me what you
discover or of course share it on
LinkedIn. That's a great place to share
it. Put it on LinkedIn. Show what you've
got and I will weigh in. I will uh add
some comments if you tag me and I will
make sure that I amplify your success.
And again, if you see other students
doing this, then please jump in yourself
and add some comments to theirs as well.
That really helps amplify the whole
community if we're there to support each
other. Okay, it's time for a wrap- up.
It's time for us to go into the final
segment. Stay for the final segment
because it's always good to wrap things
up. But unfortunately, this is the
tearful moment when we finish things
off. And what better place to finish
things off than going back again to the
Andre Carpathy tweet that started this
whole course. And I'm going to read it
to you one more time, but this time this
time it's it's like it's like I'm
speaking to you in a foreign language at
the beginning and then the end once
you've learned all of the vocabulary.
Hopefully it all will fall into place.
Andre says, "I've never felt this much
behind as a programmer. Profession is
being refactored as the bits contributed
by a programmer are becoming sparse. I
could be 10 times more powerful if I
could just string together everything
that's become available. There's a new
layer of abstraction to master with
agents, sub aents, their prompts,
context, memory, modes, permissions,
tools, plug-in skills, hooks, MCP, LSPs,
SL commands, workflows, idees, and the
need to build an all-encompassing mental
model for the strengths and pitfalls of
fundamentally stochcastic, fallible,
unintelligible, and changing entities.
Uh clearly a powerful alien tool was
handed around except it comes with no
manual and everyone has to figure out
how to operate it. Uh while the
resulting magnitude 9 earthquake is
rocking the profession. Roll up your
sleeves to not fall behind. So obviously
the bad news is that it's not like I've
given you total transparency and clarity
because this world is moving so fast and
when we look at things like guest town
it still feels completely bewildered for
me let alone for you. Uh, so yes, it is
a bit crazy out there, but I do hope at
least now that you've dimensioned the
landscape. you've got a good sense of
like things like plugins and skills and
when to use each and you've got that
hands-on experience working first of all
in the IDE but then of course in the
CLIs with claw code or codecs and now
you know about things things that that
Andre didn't even mention like
sandboxing that's so important and
powerful and how you can use that with
YOLO mode and you know about Ralph loops
and now you also know about GSD you know
about all these different bits and
pieces uh and and you've experimented
with them and that's perhaps the most
important thing that I have to say to
you, the single most important thing is
you need to be willing to experiment.
There's not necessarily one right
answer. The great thing about using
these coding agents is you can kick it
off, let it build something. If it all
goes wrong, just simply start again, try
it again with a different approach. As
you think about the approaches, keep
this chart in mind. I know I've gone
this through this like a 100 times, but
typically for more mission critical
stuff, large code bases, for code that
is at the forefront, so it may not be in
much of the uh coding agents, training
data, keep to the top row, the yellow,
look at at managing with lots of
markdown files, taking things very
incrementally. And the top right, STD,
spec driven design, that's things like
GSD. It's it's worlds where you work
step by step through a clear workflow.
that kind of approach and a trust but
verify mindset. And if you're doing
MVPs, new build, you've got some risk
appetite, you're churning out
boilerplate code, go for the purples,
yolo, but in a sandbox in something like
sprite.dev uh or or in like a managed
claude on the web. YOLO, use Ralph loops
perhaps. And then the whole idea of
multi- aent swarms and orchestration
that we've been doing the last couple of
days. And to give you some of the big
takeaways, you should pick the right
coding agent and the workflow to use
based on how mature the project is and
and what sort of risk appetites you
have, your personal skills, what's going
to suit. If you're if you're if you're a
seasoned pro, then you're probably
leaning towards the CLI tools. If you're
still getting used to this and maybe the
idees are going to feel more comfortable
for you and just your preference, like
the the mode of work that you enjoy.
Some people just love working in CLIs
and some people just prefer having the
interactivity of an IDE and you also
potentially get get familiar with some
of the models. You might just like
Claude. It might just work for you. It
works for me. And then follow these
steps. First thing to look at is the
plugins. Plugins. It's easy to look at
the official plugins and pick the most
popular ones or the ones that out of the
most popular ones that that were going
to work for your project like feature
dev or the one that simplifies code or
that builds professional front ends.
Pick the plugins are going to work for
you. And then next up, typically skills
is the next thing to do. Picking skills
are going to really work nicely for your
project. And this is also an opportunity
to use an MCP server if there are MCP
servers like Contact 7, uh, which is
which is exactly what you need. Um,
although there's also the the plug-in
for that, too. And then just be willing
to do trial and error. Just have that
experimenters mindset. Kick it off, see
what happens. If it's not going to work
for you, you can just throw it away and
go back. Uh, and having that mindset is
just so critical. And obviously make
heavy use of Git. It is your friend. It
gives you such an easy ability to go
back to where you were and also be
disciplined about markdown docs. Get
things to write to markdown. Use that as
as it sort of baked into some of these
workflows. Use it as your way of
tracking what's going on just as we've
been doing both in in weeks two and
three. That is such a great process. And
on that on that note, also just
generally manage your context. Include
code. Do slash context all the time. See
what's going on. Don't wait for your
contacts to to compact. Manage it
yourself. Write stuff out to markdown.
Write stuff to claude.md or agents.mmd
and then do a/clear to start again and
be fresh with your contacts. Being
proactive about context management is
just just the right way to do it. And
finally, remember you own the quality of
the code that you push. Remember that AI
PR policy from JellyFin. Keep that in
mind. This is code that you stand
behind. Don't let your coding agent
build slop. Don't let it put tons of
extra test files or read me and please
no emojis. Be ruthlessly on top of it.
Make things sharp and good quality code.
Own the code. Make sure that it is good
quality. Okay, those are the major
takeaways.